A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Communications, SG 2, Series 5 FA481
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Communications, 5
  - Publications, 5
    - Field Report - Program on Health Care in New York City - Health Coverage for Immigrants in New York - An Update on Policy Developments and Next Steps, 2002 July (Box 55, Folder 622)
    - Seniors and Prescription Drugs - Findings From A 2001 Survey of Seniors in Eight States & Press Release, 2002 July (Box 56, Folder 623, Folder 624)
    - In the Literature - Computerized Physician Order Entry Systems in Hospitals - Mandates and Incentives, 2002 July (Box 56, Folder 625)
    - In the Literature - Health Insurance Expansions for Working Families - A Comparison of Targeting Strategies, 2002 July-Aug. (Box 56, Folder 626)
    - Issue Brief - The Erosion of Employer-Based Health Coverage and the Threat to Workers' Health Care, 2002 Aug. (Box 56, Folder 627)
    - Picker/Commonwealth Program on Quality of Care for Frail Elders - Evaluation of Wellspring Model for Improving Nursing Home Quality, 2002 Aug. (Box 56, Folder 628, Folder 629)
    - Policy Brief - Stretching Federal Dollars - Policy Trade - Offs - in Designing a Medicare Drug Benefit with Limited Resources, 2002 Aug. (Box 56, Folder 630)
    - Field Report - Programs on Medicare's Future - Medicare+Choice After Five Years - Lessons for Medicare's Future - Findings From Seven Major cities, 2002 Sept. (Box 56, Folder 632, Folder 631)
    - Medicare's Disabled Beneficiaries - The Forgotten Population in the Debate Over Drug Benifits & Briefing Note, 2002 Sept. (Box 56, Folder 633)
    - Program on Child Development and Pediatric Care - Partnering with Parents to Promote the Healthy Development of Young Children Enrolled in Medicaid, 2002 Sept. (Box 56, Folder 634, Folder 635)
    - Program on Child Development and Pediatric Care - Primary Care Services - Propoting Optimal Child Development From Birth to THree Years, 2002 Sept. (Box 56, Folder 636, Folder 637)
    - Field Report - Program on Medicare's Future - Geograhic Inequality in Medicare+Choice Benefits Findings From Seven Communities, 2002 Sept. (Box 56, Folder 638)
    - Field Report - Program on Medicare's Future - Medicare+Choice in New York City - So Far, So Good & Briefing Note, 2002 Sept. (Box 57, Folder 639)
    - Health Care in New York City - Employer Health Coverage in the Empire State - An Uncertain Future, 2002 Sept. (Box 56, Folder 640, Folder 641)
    - In the Literature - Teaching Hospitals and Quality of Care - A Review of the Literature, 2002 Sept. (Box 56, Folder 642)
    - Task Force on Academic Health Centers - Financial Performance of Academic Health Center Hospitals, 1999-2002, 2002 Sept. (Box 57, Folder 643, Folder 644)
    - Field Report - Quality of Care for Underserved Populations - Cultural Competence in Health Care - Emerging Framework and Practical Approches, 2002 Oct. (Box 57, Folder 646, Folder 645)
    - Program on Medicare's Future - The Role of the Asset Test in Targeting Bemefits for Medicare Savings Programs, 2002 Oct. (Box 57, Folder 647)
    - Field Report - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Assessing State Strategies for Health Coverage Expansion - Summary of Case Studies of Oregon, Rhode Island, New Jersey, and Georgia, 2002 Nov. (Box 57, Folder 649, Folder 648)
    - In the Literature - Consumer - Driven Health Plans - Are They More Than Talk Now?, 2002 Nov. 20 (Box 57, Folder 650)
    - In the Literature - Medicaid Coverage for the Working Uninsured - The Role of State Policy, 2002 Nov.-Dec. (Box 57, Folder 651)
    - Issue Brief - Average Out - of - Pocket Health Care Cost for Medicare+Choice Enrollees Increase Substantially in 2002, 2002 Nov. (Box 57, Folder 652)
    - Program on Medicare's Future - Trends in Medicare+Choice Bebefits and Premiums, 1999-2002, 2002 Nov. (Box 57, Folder 653, Folder 654)
    - Program on Medicare's Future - Modernizing Medicare Cost - Sharing - Policy Options and Impacts on Beneficiary and Program Expenditures, 2002 Nov. (Box 57, Folder 655)
    - Escape Fire - Lessons for the Future of Health Care, 2002 Dec. (Box 58, Folder 657, Folder 656)
    - Health Care in New York City - New York Seniors and Prescription Drugs - Seniors Remain at Risk Despite State Efforts, 2002 Dec. (Box 58, Folder 658, Folder 659)
    - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Health Insurance Tax Credit - Will They Work for Women?, 2002 Dec. (Box 58, Folder 661, Folder 660)
    - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Staying Covered - The Importance of Retaining Health Insurance for Low-Income Families, 2002 Dec. (Box 58, Folder 662, Folder 663)
    - Field Report - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Building Quality into Rite Care - How Rhode Island is Improving Health care for its Low-Income Populations, 2003 Jan. (Box 58, Folder 664)
    - Field Report - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Expanding Health Insurance Coverage Creative-State Solutions for Challenging Times, 2003 Jan. (Box 58, Folder 666, Folder 665)
    - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Small But Significant Steps to Help the Uninsured, 2003 Jan. (Box 58, Folder 667, Folder 668)
    - Field Report - Task Force on the Future of Health Insurance - Approching Universal Coverage - Minnesota's Health Insurance Programs, 2003 Feb. (Box 58, Folder 670, Folder 669)
    - Picker, Harvey - A Celebration of the Life of, 2008 May 24 (Box 58, Folder 671)
    - A Stillness in the Pines - The Ecology of the Red-Cockaded Woodpecker - Robert W. Mcfarlane, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 672)
    - An Unfinished Revolution - Women and Health care in America - Emily Friedman, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 673)
    - Black Holes & Time Warps - Einsteins Outragous Legacy - Kip S. Thron, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 674)
    - Critical Issues in U. S. Health Reform - Eli Ginzberg, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 675)
    - Directory of Commonwealth Fund and Harkness Fellows 1925-1990 (Box 60, Folder 676)
    - Edward Stephen Harkness 1874-1940 - James W. Wooster, Jr., 1949 Jan. (Box 60, Folder 677)
    - Health Services Research - Key to Health Policy - Eli Ginzberg, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 678)
    - Life as a Geological Force - Dynamics of the Earth - Peter Westbroek, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 679)
    - Medicare Policy - New Directions for Health and Long-Term Care - Davis, Karen & Rowland, Diane, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 681, Box 60, Folder 680)
    - New Approches to the Medicare Crisis - Proceedings of the 1981 Commonwealth Fund Forum, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 682)
    - Oasis in Space - Earth History From the Beginning - Preston Cloud, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 683)
    - Order Out of Chaos - John Shaw Billings and America's Coming of Age - Carleton B. Chapman, 1992 (Box 61, Folder 684)
    - Politics, Science and Dread Disease - A Short History of U. S. Medical Research Policy - Harvard, Stephen P. Strickland, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 685, Folder 686)
    - Science and the Quiet Art - The Roll of Medical Research in Health Care - David Weatherall, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 687-688)
    - The Commonwealth Fund - Historical Sketch 1918-1962, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 689)
    - The Living-At-Home Program Innovations in Service Access and Case Management - Bogdonoff, Hughes, Weissert, and Paulsen, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 690)
    - Through the Patient's Eyes - Understanding and Promoting Patient-Centered Care - Gerteis, Edgman, Levitan, Daley & Delbanco, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 691)
    - Toward the Habbit of Truth - A Life in Science - Mahlon Hoagland, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 692)
  - Communications Audiovisual Materials, 1996 - 1998; 6
    Scope and Contents
    Contains various videos relating to the Commonwealth Fund, including camera originals and production elements for a Commonwealth Fund 80th Anniversary video, circa 1998.
    Sound recordings; Moving Images
    - APHA Video - Edited Master, 1996; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11158)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please see a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - Holiday Reception Video, 1995 December; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11159)
    - Kaiser/ Commonwealth Low Income Coverage and Access Project - New York Focus Group - Tampa Focus Group, 1997 June 11, 18; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11160)
    - AHSR - Video, 1997; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11161)
    - MLR Communications - Board Meeting, 1997 July; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11162)
    - Board Video, 1997 April; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11163)
    - The Commonwealth Fund: Boston Interviews - Tape 1, 1998 July 8; Betacam SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11164)
    - The Commonwealth Fund: Boston Interviews - Tape 2, 1998 July 8; Betacam SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11165)
    - The Commonwealth Fund: New York Interviews - Karen Davis, Tape 3, 1998 August 11; Betacam SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11166)
    - The Commonwealth Fund: New York Interviews - Karen Davis and M. Mahoney, Tape 4, 1998 August 11; Betacam SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11167)
    - The Commonwealth Fund: New York Interviews - Mahoney and Ratzenberg, Tape 5, 1998 August 11; Betacam SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11168)
    - The Commonwealth Fund: New York B-Roll, Tape 6, 1998 August 11; Betacam SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11169)
    - The Commonwealth Fund: New York B-Roll - Tape 7, 1998 August 11; Betacam SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11170)
    - The Commonwealth Fund: Photos, etc. - Tape 1 of 4, 1998 September 22; Betacam SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11171)
    - The Commonwealth Fund: Photos, etc. - Tape 2 of 4, 1998 September 22; Betacam SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11172)
    - The Commonwealth Fund: Photos, etc. - Tape 3 of 4, 1998 September 22; Betacam SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11173)
    - The Commonwealth Fund: Photos, etc. - Tape 4 of 4, 1998 September 22; Betacam SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11174)
    - The Commonwealth Fund: New York Shoot, 1998 September 28; Betacam SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11175)
    - Columbia Presbyterian - Medical Center Air Footage, 1998; Betacam SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11176)
    - The Commonwealth Health: 2nd Still Shoot - Tape 5, 1998 October 19; Betacam SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11177)
    - The Commonwealth Health: 2nd Still Shoot - Tape 6, 1998 October 19; Betacam SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11178)
    - The Commonwealth Health: 2nd Still Shoot - Tape 7, 1998 October 19; Betacam SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11179)
    - The Commonwealth Health: 2nd Still Shoot - Tape 8, 1998 October 19; Betacam SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11180)
    - The Commonwealth Fund: 80th Anniversary Video - New Narration Master, 1998; Betacam SP (Box 1, Tape AV 11181)
    - The Commonwealth Fund: Scratch Track, 1998 September 25; MiniDV (Box 1, Tape AV 11183)
    - The Commonwealth Fund: Stills and Title Stand, 1995 September 25; MiniDV (Box 1, Tape AV 11184)
      Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact an RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - The Commonwealth Fund: 80th Anniversary Video - C&C Visual - Voice Overs, 1998 October 21, 1998 October 26; DAT (Box 1, Tape AV 11182)
    - Audio Interviews for 80th Anniversary Video: MEM - Ellen Rautinberg, Karin Davis, 1998 September; Audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 11185)
  - Special Formats, 7; 4 Cubic Feet
    - Career Beginnings Summer Program, 1987; 2015:FA481:044 (Box SF1)
    - Claudia Dowling, 1985-1986; 2015:FA4810:45 (Box SF1)
    - Commonwealth Fund Agency Group, 1987; 2015:Fa481:046 (Box SF1)
    - Commonwealth Fund Executives Group, 1987; 2015:FA481:047 (Box SF1)
    - Commonwealth Fund Fellows Group, 1987; 2015:FA481:048 (Box SF1)
    - Commonwealth Fund Share Group, 1987; 2015:FA481:049 (Box SF1)
    - Minorities Program Group, 1987; 2015:FA481:050 (Box SF1)
    - Annual Report 1988 - Contact Sheets - Career Beginnings, 2015:FA481:051 (Box SF1)
    - Annual Report 1988 - Contact Sheets - Children's Store Front, 2015:FA481:052 (Box SF1)
    - Annual Report 1988 - Contact Sheets - Duplicates - Not a Complete Set, 2015:FA481:053 (Box SF1)
    - Annual Report 1988 - Contact Sheets - Elderly, 2015:FA481:054 (Box SF1)
    - Annual Report 1988 - Contact Sheets - Harkness Fellowships, 2015:FA481:055 (Box SF2)
    - Annual Report 1988 - Contact Sheets - Miscellaneous, 2015:FA481:057 (Box SF2)
    - Annual Report 1988 - Contact Sheets - National Medical Fellowships, 2015:FA481:058 (Box SF2)
    - Book Program Photos - Preston Cloud Reception, 1988; 2015:FA481:059 (Box SF2)
    - Fellows, 1988; 2015:FA481:060 (Box SF2)
    - Saving Lives Conference, 1988; 2015:FA481:061 (Box SF2)
    - N Y U - Hospital Doctors and Nurses Program, 1987-1989; 2015:FA481:062 (Box SF2)
    - Commonwealth Fund-Picker Patient-Centered Care Program, 1988-1989; 2015:FA481:063 (Box SF2)
    - Alternatives - Varying Exposure and or Contrast - Advancing Well Being of the Elderly, 1989; 2015:FA481:064 (Box SF2)
    - Alternatives - Varying Exposure and or Contrast - Career Beginnings, 1989; 2015:FA481:065 (Box SF3)
    - Alternates - Varying Exposure and or Contrast - Children's Storefront, 1989; 2015:FA481:066 (Box SF3)
    - McFarland Unified School District, 1989 May; 2015:FA481:067 (Box SF3)
    - Christmas Reception, 1993 Dec.; 2015:FA481:068 (Box SF4)
    - New York Junior Tennis League, 1993-1994; 2015:FA481:069 (Box SF4)
    - Christmas Reception - Fund 75th - Margaret E. Mahoney Leaves the Fund, 1994 December; 2015:FA481:070 (Box SF4)
    - Kip Thorne - Book Reception, 1994; 2015:FA481:071 (Box SF5)
    - Carter, Linda - Reception, 1995 Jan. 26; 2015:FA481:072 (Box SF6)
    - Commonwealth Fund - Aging Conference, 1995 Feb. 7; 2015:FA481:073 (Box SF6)
    - Atlantic Fellowships Orientation, Harkness House, 1995 March 3; 2015:FA481:074 (Box SF5)
    - Joint Center for Political And Economic Studies, 1995; 2015:FA481:075 (Box SF7)
    - New York Academy of Medicine Symposium, 1995; 2015:FA481:076 (Box SF7)
    - Staff Retreat, 1995; 2015:FA481:077 (Box SF7)
    - Staff Holiday Party, 1995 Dec.; 2015:FA481:078 (Box SF7)
    - Holiday Reception, 1995 Dec. 15; 2015:FA481:079 (Box SF7)
    - The Commonwealth Fund and The Alliance for Health Reform, 1995-1997; 2015:FA481:080 (Box SF7)
    - Minority Health Fellows, 1996; 2015:FA481:081 (Box SF7)
    - UHF - Health Briefing, 1996; 2015:FA481:082 (Box SF7)
    - Atlantic Fellowships, 1996 April 12; 2015:FA481:083 (Box SF7)
    - New York Academy of Medicine Symposium, 1996 May; 2015:FA481:084 (Box SF8)
    - Board Retreat - Cumberland Lodge - Queen Mother at Community Flower Show, 1996 July; 2015:FA$81:085 (Box SF8)
    - MEM Unveiling, 1996 Sept.; 2015:FA481:086 (Box SF8)
    - Staff Seminar, 1996 Sept.; 2015:FA481:087 (Box SF8)
    - Atlantic Symposium on Women's Mental Health, 1996 Oct.; 2015:FA481:088 (Box SF8)
    - Holiday Reception, 1996 Dec.; 2015:FA481:090 (Box SF8)
    - Holiday Reception, 1996 Dec.; 2015:FA481:091 (Box SF9)
    - Harvard University - Institute of Politics, 1996 Dec. 27; 2015:FA481:092 (Box SF9)
    - British Embassy Reception, 1997 Feb. 7; 2015:FA481:093 (Box SF9)
    - Theatre, 1997 Feb. 24; 2015:FA481:094 (Box SF9)
    - Annual Meeting on Health and Human Services Philanthropy, 1997 Feb. 27-28; 2015:FA481:095 (Box SF9)
    - Minority Health Fellows, 1997; 2015:FA481:096 (Box SF9)
    - New York Academy of Medicine Symposium, 1997; 2015:FA481:097 (Box SF9)
    - Adolescent Health Symposium, 1997 May; 2015:FA481:098 (Box SF9)
    - Chambers Reception - NCCU, 1997 July; 2015:FA481:099 (Box SF9)
    - Board Retreat, 1997 July; 2015:FA481:100 (Box SF9)
    - Staff Retreat, 1997 Aug. 1; 2015:FA481:101 (Box SF10)
    - 180th Anniversary Charles Darwin Associates Annual Meeting and Dinner - New York Academy of Sciences, 1997 Sept. 25, Nov. 14; 2015:FA481:102 (Box SF10)
    - Adolescent Girls Health National Survey - Washington, D.C., 1997 Oct.; 2015:FA481:103 (Box SF10)
    - Editors' Briefing, 1997 Nov.; 2015:FA481:104 (Box SF10)
    - Holiday Reception, 1997 Dec.; 2015:FA481:105 (Box SF10)
    - Grantmakers in Health Reception, 1996 Oct.; 2015:FA481:089 (Box SF8)
    - Commonwealth Fund Presidents - Margaret E. Mahoney and Karen Davis, 1990-1995; 2015:FA481:106 - 2015:FA481:107 (Box SF10)
    - Teenage Career Beginnings - Chemistry, 1985-1989; 2015:FS481:108 (Box SF10)
    - Miscellanous Graphic Materials, 1980-1998; 2015:FA481:109 (Box SF10)
    - Stanford Planning Grant Memo - Blue Prints, 1959 January 27-29; 2015:FA481:110 (Box SF10)
    - Miscellaneous Images (Box SF11)